Martin, Albert, Papers /3051
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Albert Martin Papers
1945-1970
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Martin, Albert
/3051
38 cubic feet
38 linear ft.
Papers (documents).
Materials on interviewing, training, worker eduction, job safety, and performance evaluation.
3075610
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, July 23, 2015
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 21, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3085: ILR School Dean's Office Files 5227: Edward Northup Hay Papers 5730: John H. Cornehlsen Papers 5928: Elaine Leeder Collection of Rose Pesotta Papers 5928av: Rose Pesotta Audio-Visual Materials 6036-027: Elaine Leeder "The Gentle Warrior: Rose Pesotta, Anarchist and Labor Organizer" Dissertation 6255: Richard Sears Barrett Papers
Martin, Albert,1909-1967.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Faculty.
3075610
- Film Manuals, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Steps Prepar. Study Course (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Management Development: Goodyear, 1953-1954 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Indiv. Needs in M.D., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- How Install MD: Appley, 1950 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Sales Training, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- National Institute of Labor Education (Box 1, Folder 7)
- On-the-Job Training: Review, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Work Staplification: A Brief Reading List, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- TWI in Japan (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Course Sup'ors (AVML), 1946 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Trends in M.D. (Box 1, Folder 12)
- AT&T Training, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Case Studies: Writing (Box 1, Folder 14)
- 8 Weeks Course for Human Relations R. Campbell, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Training in Economics, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- M.D. Outlines, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- National Foremen's Institute, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Executive Institute on Humanities, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Partic Decision- Making (Box 1, Folder 20)
- MTN in Exec. Jobs (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Elliott Service for, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Studies: Qual's Good Sup'or (Q), 1956 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Effective Supervision, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Check List JIT (Box 1, Folder 25)
- AMA Survey: M.D., 1955 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Salesman Training (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Executive Planning (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Texas A&M Extension Courses, 1957-1958 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Permission to Think, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Revol. In Mgt. Thinking, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Supervisory Training, 1952 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Executives: Qualities and Problems, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Evaluation of Training, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Philosophy of Training, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Training Course: Ind. Tr. (Box 1, Folder 36)
- The Supervisor's Job, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Human Relations Boon or Bogle Report, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Human Relations Research, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Manag. Class Society?, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Limits to HR in Supervisor, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Management Address: How to as a Failure, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Search Ingt. Phil, 1957 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Demoe. And Aut'ic Leader, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Resistance to Change, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Motivation: Job Satis., Productivity I, 1961 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Manag. Train by Committee (Box 1, Folder 47)
- SIHR (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Xceleon Rubber Company Background and Description (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Churchill Manufacturing Company: Problem in Industrial Relations: Safety (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Job Safety Analysis and On-The-Job Instruction: Cases I- III (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Patterned Exit Interview, 1953 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Industrial Organization and Safety: Case Studies (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Industrial Safety Consultants Course: Job Safety Analysis, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Accident Analysis Chart (Box 2, Folder 7)
- A Checklist for Accident Analysis (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Analysis of Workmen's Compensation Insurance Costs, Company XYZ (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Case Study in Construction Safety: Mine Accident, Problem and Answer (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Safety Inspection Check List (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Role-Playing: The Case of the Safety Belt from "Psychology in Industry" by Maier (Box 2, Folder 12)
- College Conference Sponsored by US Department of Labor, Union College, Schenectady, NY, Nov.17th, List of Conferees, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- The Ten Axioms of Accident Prevention- H.W. Heinrich (Industrial Accident Prevention) (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Sports Dugout, Inc. Background and Questions (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Case Study: The Washington Foundry, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Citation Number I Appearing in "Employers' Compensation Liability for Physically Handicapped Workers" (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Table of Scheduled Changes- A. For Loss of Member- Traumatic or Surgical, B. Impairment of Function (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Principles for Safe Plant Operation (Box 2, Folder 19)
- News Clippings- New York Times (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Black Clawson Paper and Oher Paper Companies Pamphlets, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- Link Aviation: A General Precisions Company, Flight Training Simulators, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 3)
- General Precision Group Pamphlets (Box 3, Folder 4)
- The National Bank and Trust Company of Norwich and Bennett- Ireland Inc. Pamphlets, 1956 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- The Raymond Corporation (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Endicott Johnson Shoe Corporation Pamphlet and Related Material, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- New York Stock Exchange Pamphlets and an Intro to Supreme Court Decision Making by Harold J. Spaeth (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Pamphlets and Reports on Education Locally and Abroad, 1959-1964 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Hallift, Hall Ski- Lift Company and Other Ski Lift Companies (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Guidelines and Articles on Good Management Skills Including Training and Leadership (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Prospects for Organization of White- Collar Workers by Albert Blum, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Dr. Albert Martin Correspondence, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Industrial Bulletin Sept. 1964- Dec. 1965, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Notes (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Student Voluntary Education Rating Scale (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Fair Labor Standards Act/Reporting and Disclosure Act/Welfare and Pension Disclosure Act Pamphlets (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Industrial Relations Center, University of Minnesota Papers Reprints 38-40, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Seminar on Introductory Sociology, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Supervisory Questionnaire, Checklist for Use of Trainer in Constructive Analysis of Instruction Demonstration (Box 3, Folder 20)
- NYSEG Publications, News and Annual Reports, 1956-1957 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Religious News: Christian Economics 1964, Symbolism in Worship 1948, Christianity Today 1964-1965, 1948-1965 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Articles and Exercises on Management (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Case Studies and Exercises on Labor Management (Box 3, Folder 24)
- General Electric Annual Report, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Questionnaire (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Syracuse University Alumni news, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Standard Oil Company, Eastman Kodak, General Motors, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Urban Renewal, New York City Planning Commission, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Gould's News, The Story of Coke and Coal Chemicals from American Coke and Coal Chemicals Institute, 1957 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- NYSSILR Current Issues in Labor Arbitration, Reports, and ILR Research, 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- He Fair Labor Standards Act as Applied to Retailers of Goods or Services and "How to Get Facts You Need", 1956-1961 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Small Business Administration; What it is, What it Does. Supplemental Unemployment Benefit Plan, and Employees' Health Insurance Program, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- A Basic Reading List on Banking Topics and Employment Service Review on Agriculture, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Misc. Articles and Reports from Cornell, Harvard and Elsewhere, 1954-1963 (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Saturday Review 1965, and Colloquium, Fall 1965 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Correspondence, 1962-1965 (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Miscellaneous (Box 3, Folder 38)
- National Metal Trades Assoc. Form (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Job Analysis and Evaluation, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Allen Wales Form, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Merit Rating and Executive Appraisal, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Appraisal Check List, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Esso Standard Oil Development Program, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Industrial Psychology Forms (Box 4, Folder 7)
- AVMC Forms (Box 4, Folder 8)
- The Critical Incident Method (Flannigan), 1955 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Self - Analysis for Su'pors, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Role Playing - Unsatisfactory Efficiency Interview (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Eval. Of Supervisors" Form, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Creole's Performance Rating, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Self-Evaluation: Managing (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Committee Appraisal: Sup'or, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Mgt. Salary Admin., 1958 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Patterned Merit Review Dartnell (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Ind. Rel. Reading List (Misc.), 1960 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Praeger, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Congress Comes to the Classroom (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Major Social Problems - Earl Raab and Gertrude Selznick (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Southern Illinois University Press (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Books for Colleges and Seminaries, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- The Princeton Studies (Box 4, Folder 24)
- The Free Press of Glencoe - Catalogue of Publications, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Humanities - Prentice-Hall, 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Textbooks in Business and Economics (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Business Trends and Progress, 1965 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Tests, Materials and Services, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Colloquium, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Books for Colleges, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- The Discussion Leadership Center (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Readers Report, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Schools and Colleges, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Value and Price, 1962 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Scholarly Books in America, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Trained Men, 1961 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Major Social Problems, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 38)
- College Information Service Publication Test - General Electric, 1963 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- AMA Summer Program 1961 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Off-the-Job Safety Questionnaire Reponses, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Principles of Man Power Development and Job Training, 1955-1958 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Case Studies on Employee- Management Relations, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Getting Results Through Other People (Box 5, Folder 4)
- H.R> Crane Math Reviews University of Michigan, 1962-1965 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Labor- Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Human Motivation, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Employment Interview and New York State Unemployment Insurance Quiz (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Communication and Administering Changes, 1954-1957 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- The Managing Process and Decision Making, 1956-1957 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Management Development and Improvement, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Analyzing Work Climate and the Character of a Company, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Table of Scheduled Charges and Citation No.1 Appearing in "Employers' Compensation Liability for Physically Handicapped Workers", 1957 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Harvard Business School, Century Company; Leadership Behavior, Worker Relationships and Satisfaction (Box 5, Folder 14)
- On and Off the Job Safety ad Saving Pamphlets, 1955-1958 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Union Carbide Electro Metallurgical Company Safety, 1956-1958 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Off-the-Job Safety Questionnaire Responses, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- "Off-the-Job" Safety Kit Materials (Pamphlets and Reports), 1957 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Off-the-Job Safety Promotion and Movement, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- "Off-the-Job" Safety Questionnaire Responses, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- "Off-the-Job" Safety Questionnaire Responses, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- "Off-the-Job" Safety Questionnaire Responses, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- The Pure Oil News Nay-August 1957 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- "Off-the-Job" Safety Questionnaire Responses, 1957 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Misc. Safety Related News and Press Releases, 1957-1960 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- History of Ethics Reviews Outlines (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Moral Ideals Pre-Soc. Period (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Neoplatonism (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Socrates + Plato (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Aristotle (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Christian Ethics of Salvation (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Medieval Culture + the Scholastic Method (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Modern Ethics of French Revolution (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Moral Peril + Social Order (Box 6, Folder 9)
- British Moralists (Box 6, Folder 10)
- French Rationalism (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Ethics of Spinoza (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Locke's Confused Position on Ethics (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Conscience of Moral Law (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Moral Sense Theories (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Early British (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Ethics of Sympathy (Box 6, Folder 19)
- French Enlightment Voltaire- Rousseai- Mater'ise (Box 6, Folder 20)
- On Eae Fo. Rival. (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Lessing to Gaetle (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Ethics - Idealism (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Ethics of Pessimism (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Realistic Reaction Ethics (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Growth British Liberalism (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Early New England (Box 6, Folder 27)
- French Positivism (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Social + Relig. Crit. + Moral Bearing (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Revival of Idealism (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Ethical Issues in Contemp. Thought (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Epicureanism + Stoicism + Neoplatonism (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Bentham of Mill (Box 6, Folder 33)
- John Dewey (Box 6, Folder 34)
- H. Spencer (Box 6, Folder 35)
- T. Hobbes (Box 6, Folder 36)
- T. Aguinas (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Bergson (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Hobbes Leviathan (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Locke's Treaties of Gov't. (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Morality + Religion (+ Art) (Box 6, Folder 41)
- R.B. Perry (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Henry Sidgwick Methods of Ethics (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Calvinism + (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Ethics of Rant (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Critique of Pure Reason (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Phil. Of Aufularuns (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Miscellaneous, 1955-1957 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Student Aid Annual, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- Teaching and Learning, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Lecture in Training, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Types of Disc. Plans, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Better Use MD: Programs R, 1955 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Training in Ind. Course for Students, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Conf.: Day Self. And Understanding (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Top Manag. And Training, 1956 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Univ. E. D. Program, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Teaching Methods of Unions, 1957 (Box 6, Folder 58)
- Learning Process (Box 6, Folder 59)
- Newspaper Clippings (Boxed), 1955-1959 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Boxed
- Misc. Letters, 1960-1965 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Leadership in Supervision (Box 8, Folder 1)
- What Employees Expect (Box 8, Folder 2)
- How Exec's. Handle People (HBR) (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Across Departmental Frontiers (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Education in Econ. Industry (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Research in Human Relation, 1954 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Brain Power Tests: Exec., 1958 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Supervisory for General (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Company tr. Programs, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- What Foremen Want in Tr., 1957 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- 1st M.D. Program (M.I.T.), 1957 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Criticism of M.D. Programs, 1954-1956 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- M.D. Retail Stores, 1950 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Course Supervisors: Outline (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Humorous Exec. Rating (Box 8, Folder 15)
- Human Relations Research, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 16)
- Evaluation of Training, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 17)
- Case Studies Man. Dev., 1954 (Box 8, Folder 18)
- Management Development: Outlines, 1957 (Box 8, Folder 19)
- Industrial Research Universities, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 20)
- Results Through Others (Box 8, Folder 21)
- Research Leadership Supervision (Box 8, Folder 22)
- Effective Human Relations (Box 8, Folder 23)
- Instructor's Clinic - IBM (Box 8, Folder 24)
- Tips of Interviewing, 1960 (Box 8, Folder 25)
- Techniques of Interviewing Employment (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Techniques of Interviewing (Box 8, Folder 27)
- Techniques of Interview (Box 8, Folder 28)
- Techniques of Interviewing Employment (Box 8, Folder 29)
- Class Material - Techniques of Interviewing (Box 8, Folder 30)
- 8 Weeks Short Course Technique of Interviewing, 1952 (Box 8, Folder 31)
- Handouts Interviewing Lots (Box 8, Folder 32)
- Employees of Interviewing (Box 8, Folder 33)
- Interviewing: Listening (Box 8, Folder 34)
- Employment Interviewing, 1956 (Box 8, Folder 35)
- Corning Glass Management Program, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- "Management Workshop", 1955 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Case: The Mine Accident, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Case: The Mine Accident, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- Management Course for University Supervisors, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- Memorandum, 1957 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Cornell Fire Safety Conf. Talb 6/62, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Orientation + Training Crowley Milk G. 1 Day Seminar, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Crowley Milk Co., 1962 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Orientation and Training Seminar, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Orientation on Training Seminar, 1962 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Industrial Relations Seminar, 1956 (Box 9, Folder 12)
- Industrial Safety Course ILR 362 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- JIT Cards, 1951 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Course at NCV Fundamentals of Effective Supervision, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- NSC Fertileger Section Conference, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Crowley Milk Co., 1961 (Box 9, Folder 17)
- Norwich Industries (Box 9, Folder 18)
- Course: Personnel Admin. + the First Line, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 19)
- Conference for Management Executives on Building and Effective Management Team, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 1)
- A Guide for the Selection of Supervisors- The Detroit Edison Company, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Induction of New Employees, 1956-1961 (Box 10, Folder 3)
- Better Selection of potential Executives- Address, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 4)
- Selection and Development of Supervisory Personnel, 1956-1957 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- "The Rorschach Test" by Gary Byrn Psychology 102 Prof. Mason, 1962 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Dartnell Training Conference- Personnel Selection, 1952-1957 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Tested Techniques of Personnel Selection- Dartnell, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Tested Techniques of Personnel Selection- Dartnell, 1955 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Patterned Interview- Dartnell Corporation, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 10)
- Telephone Check with Schools- Dartnell Corporation, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Application for Position- Dartnell Corporation, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Telephone Check- Dartnell Corporation, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Personnel Test, Test of Mechanical Comprehension (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Application for Employment- National Cash Register Company, Welch Allyn Inc., and Probation Notice for Cash Register Company (Box 10, Folder 15)
- "Complete" Job-Test Package for Inspector (Box 10, Folder 16)
- "Complete" Job-Test Package for Semi- Skilled Workers (Box 10, Folder 17)
- Notes (Box 10, Folder 18)
- Case Study Job Applications: Planter, Tyler, Jenkins (Box 10, Folder 19)
- Selection and Evaluation Summary- Case Studies (Box 10, Folder 20)
- Test of Mechanical Comprehension Rights and Wrongs Keys (Box 10, Folder 21)
- The Employment Function (Box 10, Folder 22)
- Developing a Better Personnel Selection Program, Tips on Employment Interviewing (Box 10, Folder 23)
- Driver Interview Materials (Box 10, Folder 24)
- Physical Records and Examination- Drivers (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Application Materials for Sales Position- Dartnell Corporation, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 26)
- Application for Executive Position, 1958-1959 (Box 10, Folder 27)
- Patterned Interview Form- Dartnell, 1959 (Box 10, Folder 28)
- Investigator's Cost Data Sheet and Department Supervisor's Accident Cost Report (Box 10, Folder 29)
- Supervisor Accident Report (Box 10, Folder 30)
- Accident Analysis Chart (Box 10, Folder 31)
- Six Point Safety Program, Discovering Causes, Effecting Cures (Box 10, Folder 32)
- Industrial Organization and Safety- Case Studies, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 33)
- Analysis of Workmen's Compensation Insurance Costs, Company XYZ, 1956 (Box 10, Folder 34)
- Raymond Metal Company Case Study, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 35)
- Job Safety Analysis and On-the-Job Instruction, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 36)
- The Case of James Montgomery, 1957 (Box 10, Folder 37)
- List for Tour of Science Park Syracuse and "The Practice of Management", 1963 (Box 10, Folder 38)
- Placement + Safety, 1949 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- N.Y. State Bureau of Safety, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- BLS Safety Standards - Monthly Bulletins, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Safety: Visual Aide, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Sources of Safety Help, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Safety in the Small Company, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- American Standard Association, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- American Society Safety Engineers, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Safe Practice Manuals, 1961 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- GLF Industrial Safety, 1953 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Safety Program: Socony, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- N.Y.S. Governor's Safety Conference, 1956 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Industrial Noise, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Philosophy of Accident Prevention, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Industrial Vision, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Industrial Commission Ohio (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Form Safety Handbook, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Courses by Univ., 1957 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Safety - Statistics, 1955 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Safety Program Report, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Safety Program Reports, 1953-1954 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Safety Training: Florida Ind. Comm., 1950-1954 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Company Safety Hudson Coal Company, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Company Safety Hudson Coal Company, 1954 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- College and University Safety Education, 1957 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Workmen's Compensation, 1955-1957 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Company Safety Program: Oneida Silversmiths, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- President's Occupational Conference, 1954 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Safety Directors (Box 12, Folder 3)
- State Safety Programs: Connecticut, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Safety: Letters, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- State Fund, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Human Element in Accident Prevention, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Safety Committees, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Fire Protection, 1960-1961 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Company Safety Program: Du Pont, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Company Safety Program: American Can, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Company Safety Program: R.C.A., 1957 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Company Safety Program: U.S. Steel (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Traffic Safety, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Safety Engineering, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- National Safety Council, 1956 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Construction Safety, 1957 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- School Safety, 1950 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Discussion Notes on Developing A Training Program in Accident Prevention, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Two Methods of Estimating Accident Costs and Job Analysis Schedule, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Role Playing: The Case of the Safety Line, Accident Report System, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Cardinal Points to be Remembered by Supervisors to Maintain an Effective Safety Program, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Construction Safety Consultants Course: The Accident Sequence, 1957 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Report of Accident Experience- Workmen's Compensation, Your Accident Experience, 1950 (Box 13, Folder 6)